[{"answer": "I'm sure I have a low IQ. I've been lying about my SAT scores for 15 years", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cafe.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "What did I get or what do I say I got", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What did you get", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cafe.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What do you say", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "What did I get or what do I say I got", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cafe.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I say fourteen o nine ", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "It's Latin. I read it in some book. I don't know, I just wanted to say it out loud", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cafe.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Have you gone in there", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Sure, fine", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cafe.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Get out of here", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cafe.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You get out of here", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Oh, how did you hear about us", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cafe.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Smoking or non smoking? We are proud to offer both", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Eh, people, people are talking", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cafe.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Non smoking would be great", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Look, my friend, I have to take this test ok, I don't have a long of time", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cafe.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "An IQ test", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Why do you take an IQ test", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cafe.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cafe.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Oh, it's locked", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Yeah, had some coffee, yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cafe.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Where did I get the coffee? Where do think I got the coffee, from the grocery store", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Where did you get the coffee", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cafe.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "How did you get there", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "How did you get out of the apartment? I didn't see you leave", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cafe.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "You climbed out the window", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Of course", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cafe.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "The door? Why would I go out the door? The window is right here", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Well my friend, I have to return this test. I've got to get out of here", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cafe.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I had to take it again", "qsentId": 32}]